lakequincy.com 2011-02-05

# Privacy Policy :: Lake Quincy Media

Lake Quincy Media is a Publisher-side Technology Company. Publisher-side means that all of our solutions reside on our own Web site server or the individual server of the Web sites we partner with.

  * Lake Quincy Media's technologies are not downloaded to a user's desktop.
  * Lake Quincy Media's technologies do not upload personally identifiable information from a user's desktop.
  * Lake Quincy Media's technologies do not collect or store any personally identifiable user information.

Lake Quincy Media, LLC. ("Lake Quincy Media") respects the privacy concerns of the users of its Web site, LakeQuincy.com (the "Site"). Lake Quincy Media thus provides this privacy statement to explain what information is gathered during a visit to the Site and how such information may be used. 

#### Use of Information

As a general policy no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or e-mail address, is automatically collected from your visit to the Site. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of Lake Quincy Media's Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your IP address is gathered in order to enhance your online experience. 

The Site may request that you give us contact information such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address; demographic information such as your age and gender; and personal preference information. Information submitted at the time of submission will be used by Lake Quincy Media only as necessary for our legitimate business interests, including without limitation the improvement of our products, services and the contents of the Website. Lake Quincy Media may also share such information with our business and promotional partners to further those interests. Personally identifiable information is never sold or leased to any third parties. 

#### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update it by emailing our Customer Support via our contact page (http://lakequincy.com/contact.aspx) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

#### _Lake Quincy Media's_ Inquiry Form

The Lake Quincy Media Site contains an "inquiry form" for web publishers to request additional information about Lake Quincy Media's products/services. The inquiry form requires web publishers to give contact information (such as name and email address.) Lake Quincy Media uses this information to contact Web Publishers about the services on the Site in which they have expressed interest. 

Web Publishers have the option to provide demographic information (such as Web site address and vertical sector) to Lake Quincy Media. Lake Quincy Media encourages them to submit this information so it can provide them a more customized reply to their inquiry. 

#### Insertion Orders

If an advertiser purchases a service from Lake Quincy Media, Lake Quincy Media requests certain personal and company identity information from the advertiser on the insertion form. Advertisers must provide contact information (such as name, company name, street address, email and telephone number) and financial information. Lake Quincy Media uses this information to provide services and for billing purposes. If Lake Quincy Media has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the advertiser. 

#### Web Publisher Service Agreement

If a Web Publisher signs a service agreement, Lake Quincy Media requires the Web Publisher to provide certain identifiable information including: name, company name, street address, email and telephone number. This information is necessary to process the Web Publisher's agreement. 

#### Web Publisher Sign-up form

When a Web Publisher signs a service agreement with Lake Quincy Media, the Web Publisher is also required to provide company and personal identity information, commercial information, technical contact information and customization information to start their contextual advertising services. Lake Quincy Media uses this information to provide services and for payment purposes. If Lake Quincy Media has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the Web Publisher. 

#### Advertising Network Service Agreement 

When an Advertising Network signs a service agreement with Lake Quincy Media, the Advertising Network is also required to provide company, personal identity information and commercial information. Lake Quincy Media uses this information to provide services and for payment purposes. If Lake Quincy Media has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the Advertising Network. 

#### Service-related Announcements

Lake Quincy Media will send Web Publishers service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. The only other e-mails we send out are in response to feedback, contact and sign-up form submissions. 

Generally, a Web Publisher may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If a Web Publisher does not wish to receive these communications, they have the option to deactivate their account according to the terms of their Web Services Agreement. 

#### Customer Service

Based upon the provided personally identifiable information, Lake Quincy Media will send Web Publishers a welcoming email to verify their username and password and to set up their account. Lake Quincy Media will also communicate with them in response to their inquiries, to provide the services they request, and to manage their account. Lake Quincy Media will communicate with Web Publishers by email or telephone, in accordance with their wishes. 

#### Testimonials

If your name appears in a testimonial on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information displayed there can be read, collected, or used by other users of this website, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these testimonials. 

#### Legal Disclaimer

Lake Quincy Media may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with Lake Quincy Media's rights or property, other users of the Website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Lake Quincy Media may also disclose user information when necessary to comply with a court order, legal process or other legal proceeding. 

Children Age 12 and Under: Lake Quincy Media recognizes the special obligation to protect personally identifiable information obtained from children age 12 and under. AS SUCH, IF YOU ARE 12 YEARS OLD OR YOUNGER, Lake Quincy Media REQUESTS THAT YOU NOT SUBMIT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE SITE OR TO Lake Quincy Media. If Lake Quincy Media discovers that a child age 12 or younger has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete that child's personally identifiable information from our records. 

#### Use of Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using our Site easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. These cookies are restricted for use only on our Site, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please consult the technical information relevant to your browser for instructions. If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of the Site may not function properly or may be considerably slower. 

#### Links to External Web sites

Lake Quincy Media is not responsible for the content or practices of third party Web sites not owned or controlled by Lake Quincy Media. Lake Quincy Media is also not responsible for any information that you might share with such linked websites. You should refer to each such Web site's respective privacy policy and practices prior to disclosing any such information. 

#### Choice/Opt-Out

The Site may provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us at the point where we request information about you. You always have the option of removing your name from any e-mail list in order to discontinue any such future communications. In order to ensure immediate removal from any list, please follow the specific instructions set forth within the communications you receive from Lake Quincy Media which you no longer wish to receive. If you are unsuccessful in completing the instructions specified in any such communication, please e-mail us at support AT LakeQuincy.com, including a copy of the undesired email attached to the request, and state you wish to be removed from the mailing list. 

#### Contact Information for Questions, Comments and Complaints

If you have any questions, comments or complaints about LakeQuincy.com or about this privacy statement, please contact: 

> Via mail: 
> 
> Lake Quincy Media
> 
> 250 Ferrand Drive Suite 503
> 
> Toronto, Ontario, M3C 3G8
> 
> Canada

> Via email:  
>  support AT lakequincy.com

> Via telephone:  
>  +1 416-849-8900 x 100 

Information provided by you via general e-mail inquiries to Lake Quincy Media such as your e-mail address is used only to respond to your inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never shared with third parties. 

#### Security

Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Lake Quincy Media cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit via the Internet. By transmitting any such information to Lake Quincy Media, you accept that you do so at your own risk. 

#### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using the Website, you accept the policies and restrictions set forth in this Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the Site. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

Last updated 31 July 2006
